Avishai Katz

Information System Management

Contact

Address

Haifa

Phone

052 321 1486

E-mail

avishaikatz24@gmail.com

Languages

Hebrew

English

Skills

MS Office

Java, C#, Python and SQL

Fast Learning

High-energy, organized, responsible student currently finalizing BA diploma in Information Systems Management and prepared to contribute abilities to any role while further developing acquired skills and gaining real-world experience.

Versed in Java, Python, C# and SQL.

Positively impact on operations with top-notch communication and critical thinking skills.

Flexible Employment Location.

Work History

2020-03 -

Visa Coordinator

Current

Department Of International Relations, BGU, Beer Sheva

- Providing service in English to foreign students at Ben Gurion University.
- Resolved bureaucratic problems, improved operations and provided exceptional client support.
- · Managing several projects simultaneously.

2014-01 -2017-12

Shift Manager

Nitzat HaDuvdavan, Haifa

- Devised new promotional approaches to boost customer numbers and market penetration while enhancing engagement and driving growth.
- Inventory, delivery system and checkouts management.
- Ability to work under pressure and responsibility for a variety of areas.

Education

2008-09 -2011-08

High School Diploma

Hebrew Reali School - Haifa

- Majored in Medical Biology and Extended Computer Science.
- · High Finals Average.

2018-10 -Current

BA: Information Systems Management

Ben Gurion University - Beer Sheva

Among the courses:

- Object Oriented Software Development Principles of recyclable modular software, object-oriented software design including classes and objects, error handling and anomalies, process communication and graphical user interface (GUI).
- Databases Models, normalization, relational algebra, SQL language and tools for displaying data.
- Analysis and design of information systems Atages in the development of an information system, various approaches to the life cycle of an information system, initiation of a new system, methods for collecting data, techniques for describing and documenting, initial characterization of an information system, exploration of applicability.
- Operations Research Modeling problems as linear programs, transportation and placement problems.
- · Programming courses in Java, Python , C# and SQL.
- Using various software tools such as SQL Server,
 PowerDesigner, Eclipse and Visual Studio.

Military Service

2011 - 2014 : Medic at a Military Clinic, Bahad 15, Full Service.